<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My_Project</string>


    //Facebook
    <string name="facebook_app_id">231463015515609</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb231463015515609</string>

    //*******
    <string name="jarash_Description">erash is located 48 km north of the capital city of Amman. The festival site is located within the ancient ruins of Jerash, some of which date to the Roman age (63 BC). Jerash Festival is a festival which features poetry recitals, theatrical performances, concerts and other forms of art jerash is located 48 km north of the capital city of Amman. The festival site is located within the ancient ruins of Jerash, some of which date to the Roman age (63 BC). Jerash Festival is a festival which features poetry recitals, theatrical performances, concerts and other forms of ar</string>
    <string name="nebu_Title">Nebu Mountain</string>
    <string name="nebu_Description">Mount Nebo is significant because of its role in the Old Testament. The Bible says that Mount Nebo was where Moses lived out his final days and saw the Promised Land, which he would never enter. It is said that Moses’ body may be buried here, although that has yet to be proven. There are two peaks on Mt. Nebo, Siyagha and al-Mukhayyat. By the 4th century AD, Mount Nebo had already become a pilgrimage site and a church and sanctuary were built on Siyagha to honor Moses. In the 6th century AD, monks constructed a Byzantine monastery on Siyagha, which lasted for almost six centuries. While the building is no longer there, the mosaics from this time period are still visible. The site was abandoned by the 16th century. In 1993, Mount Nebo was purchased by the Franciscans who restored the site. It is an active Franciscan monastery today that is open to visitors.</string>
    <string name="amman_Castel_Title">Amman Castle</string>
    <string name="amman_Castle_Description">Jabal al-Qalaa Castle is one of the seven mountains of the city of Amman, which the Ammonites have taken since ancient times as the seat of their rule in the city, and after them the Greeks, Romans and Byzantines who occupied the city respectively until the Islamic conquest in the seventh century AD, where the Umayyad Palace was built on its top. Jabal al-Qalaa emerged in Amman, the seat of the Ammonite capital. In which the remains of the palaces of the Ammonites are still present, including the walls of the walls, and the wells dug in the limestone. Four statues of the Ammonite kings dating back to the eighth century BC were also found in the castle mountain. There are also Roman Corinthian monuments and columns in the Citadel Mountain, and a temple to Hercules. It also contains Islamic monuments dating back to the Umayyad period, where the Umayyad Palace was there. In addition, there is the Jordanian Archaeological Museum on the top of the mountain that simulates the history of Jordan in general and Amman in particular.</string>
    <string name="roman_Title">Roman Amphitheater</string>
    <string name="roman_Description">The Roman Amphitheater is a Roman theater located in the eastern part of the Jordanian capital, Amman, specifically at the foot of Jabal Al-Joufeh, on one of the hills opposite the Amman Citadel. A Greek inscription on one of the pillars indicates that this amphitheater was built in honor of Emperor Anthony Pius, who visited Amman in 130 AD. Next to the amphitheater is the Forum Square, with a total area of ​​7,600 m². Its construction probably dates back to the second century AD, specifically between 138 AD and 161 AD during the reign of Roman Emperor Antoninus Pius. Roman amphitheater used for musical and theatrical performances. Because of the quality of its sound system, it is still used sometimes for artistic performances. The theater can accommodate 6,000 spectators, which is larger than the southern theater in Jerash, which has a capacity of 4,000-5,000 spectators. It is to this day the largest theater in Jordan. In front of the stage of the stage, which is raised by the artists, there is a certain place in the middle of the stage from which the spectators can hear the sound emanating from it in a clear way in all the stands of the stage. The stands are divided into 44 classes, in three main groups. The first group of rows was used for the loft and dignitaries, while the groups of the second and third rows were for the rest of the people. There are rooms behind the stage, which artists use to change their clothes and prepare for appearances in front of the audience</string>
    <string name="museum_Title">Dar Al Saraya Museum</string>
    <string name="museum_Description">Dar Al Saraya Museum is a Jordanian archaeological museum located in the northern city of Irbid. Its history dates back to the Ottoman era in the Levant, specifically in the mid-nineteenth century, when it was established as a fortress over the southern edge of Tell Irbid. The museum consists of seven halls, six of which are part of the original Ottoman building, consisting of a group of rooms surrounding an open courtyard. The exhibits were distributed in three large halls, according to the chronological sequence of the civilizational stages of the internationally approved Jordanian antiquities. In addition to this, there are three exhibition halls. In its plan, the building resembles the castles and inns established by the Ottomans on the Shami pilgrimage trail.</string>
    <string name="arar_Title">Arar Cultural House</string>
    <string name="arar_Description">m. Founding of the Beit Arar Museum to host cultural and cognitive events in the city. The museum is located in the house of the poet Mustafa Wahbi Al-Tal.</string>
    <string name="dibben_Title">Dibeen Forest Reserve</string>
    <string name="dibben_Description">Miyeh Dibeen is one of the nature reserves in Jordan, located in the Jerash Governorate, north of the capital, Amman. It extends over an area of 8.5 square kilometers of mountainous areas. Founded in 2004, Dibeen is considered one of the driest regions in the world where Aleppo pine grows, with an average rainfall of approximately 440 millimeters per year.</string>
    <string name="arch_Title">Hadrians Arch</string>
    <string name="arch_Description">The Arch of Hadrian or Hadrians Gate or Arch of Triumph is a triumphal arch that is one of the most famous landmarks of the Jordanian city of Jerash. It is located on the southern side of the city. It is a gate with three arches, the current height of which is 11 meters. It was erected in celebration of the visit of the Roman Emperor Hadrian to the city in the winter of the year 129-130 AD. This arch is one of several triumphal arches built in honor of Emperor Hadrian. Its height was about 22 meters when it was built. It is likely that it had wooden doors. Unconventional architectural elements - probably Nabataean - appear, including the decoration of the bases of its columns, whose capitals were made On the bottom, not on the top as usual.</string>
    <string name="artemis_Title">Temple of Artemis</string>
    <string name="artemis_Description">The Temple of Artemis in Jerash was a Roman temple in Jordan. The temple was built on one of the highest points and dominated the entire city. The ruins of the temple are still one of the most famous monuments of the ancient city of Gerasa (Jerash).</string>
    <string name="square_Title">Symposium Square</string>
    <string name="square_Description">Ruins of an ancient Roman forum</string>
    <string name="hourse_Title">Horse Field</string>
    <string name="hourse_Description"></string>
    <string name="street_Title">Columns Street</string>
    <string name="street_Description">Ra Al-Amoud or Cardo (Latin: Cardo maximus) is the main street in the ancient city of Jerash, northern Jordan. It is 800 meters long and has about a thousand columns</string>
    <string name="south_Title">Jerash South Theater</string>
    <string name="south_Description">The Southern Theater in Jerash is a Roman theater located in the archaeological area of Jerash in northern Jordan, and it is its largest theater. It was built in the first century AD, and accommodates about 3,000 - 5,000 spectators, as it was designed to fit the sound system in all its corners, which still serves as it was in the period of its construction. It is also used today in cultural and artistic events, such as the Jerash Festival.</string>
    <string name="nourth_Title">Jerash North Theatre</string>
    <string name="nourth_Description"></string>
    <string name="barqash_Title">Barqash Forests</string>
    <string name="barqash_Description">The Barqash Forest is considered one of the largest forests in Jordan in terms of area, characterized by its moderate climate in Ghalib. Many animals live there, such as: waw, wolves, wild boars, hyenas, squirrels, species of European brown deer, red foxes and wild cats. Various types of trees grow in the forests, some of which extend To the age of 4,000 years, such as pine, oak, carob, maple, linden, buckthorn, cypress, and mallow, the forest faces many dangers, most notably the cutting of trees. There are many caves in Barqash, including the 4 million-year-old back cave, which is one of the most beautiful natural caves in the world.</string>
    <string name="ajloun_Title">Ajloun Castle</string>
    <string name="ajloun_Description">Ajloun Castle, also called al-Rabad Castle and Salah al-Din Castle, is a fortress located in Ajloun, Jordan, on the top of Jabal Awf overlooking the valleys of Kafrnaja, Rajeb and al-Yabis. It was built by Commander Izz al-Din Osama, one of the leaders of Salah al-Din al-Ayyubi in 1184 AD, to be a fulcrum to protect the region and preserve the transportation and pilgrimage routes between the Levant and the Hijaz, for its supervision of the Jordan Valley and its control over the area between Lake Tiberias and the Dead Sea.</string>
    <string name="ajloun_Fourest_Title">Ajloun Forest Reserve</string>
    <string name="ajloun_Fourest_Description">Ajloun Forest Reserve is a natural reserve located in the north of the Hashemite Kingdom of Jordan in a northern part of Ajloun Governorate, 8 km north of the governorate center. This reserve was called the Zobia Reserve, located in the Barqash area within the lands of Irbid, where the brown deer breeding program began.</string>
    <string name="selaa_Title">Silaa Castle</string>
    <string name="selaa_Description">Al Sila Castle is a product of an Arab civilization that extends back to 1200 BC, and contains palaces, caves, models of art, sculpture and architecture, amazing irrigation systems and watchtowers at a height</string>
    <string name="aqaba_Castel_Title">Aqaba Castle</string>
    <string name="aqaba_Castle_Description">Aqaba Castle is an ancient castle located in the center of the city of Aqaba in southern Jordan, specifically on the shore of the Gulf of Aqaba. This castle dates back to the end of the Mamluk era in the region, but today it has been turned into a museum. One of the highlights of the castle is the Aqaba mast. It was built in 2004 in the square adjacent to the castle to carry the flag of the Great Arab Revolt. At that time, the mast was the tallest in the world.</string>
    <string name="ayla_Title">Ayla Oasis</string>
    <string name="ayla_Description">Ayla Resorts is a $1.4 billion redevelopment project in Aqaba in southern Jordan. It consists of artificial lakes aimed at adding 17 new kilometers of beachfront, 1,700 hotel rooms, and 3,000 residential units, and will host Jordans first green golf course. Designed by Greg Norman, this 18-hole golf course is considered one of the most environmentally friendly golf courses in the world. The resort is located in the Hyatt Regency Aqaba Ayla Hotel, which contains 286 modern rooms, including 37 luxurious suites, in addition to one princely suite and one royal suite.</string>
    <string name="beach_Title">South Beach</string>
    <string name="beach_Description">Tourists and locals both gather to relax on the sand and have a good time swimming in the warm crystal waters of this beautiful beach.#</string>
    <string name="petra_Title">Petra</string>
    <string name="petra_Description">Petra or Petra is an archaeological and historical city located in the Maan Governorate in the south of the Hashemite Kingdom of Jordan. It is famous for its rock-cut architecture and ancient aqueduct system. It was called in the past "Sela", as it was called the "Pink City" due to the colors of its twisted rocks. Petra was founded approximately in 312 BC as the capital of the Nabataean kingdom. It assumed a prominent position for many years, as its location on the Silk Road, and the Mediterranean for the civilizations of Mesopotamia, Palestine and Egypt, played a major role that made the Nabatean state control the trade between the civilizations of these regions and their inhabitants. The city is located on the slopes of the altar mountain, among a group of towering rocky mountains, which form the northwestern flank of the Arabian Peninsula, specifically Wadi Araba, which extends from the Dead Sea to the Gulf of Aqaba.</string>
    <string name="amra_Title">Amra Palace</string>
    <string name="amra_Description">Qasr Amra or Qasir Amra is an Umayyad desert palace located in the north of the Jordanian desert in the Azraq area in the Zarqa Governorate, about 85 km east of Amman. The basic rules of organizational units in 1985 AD.</string>
    <string name="reserve_Title">Shaumari Reserve</string>
    <string name="reserve_Description">The first wildlife sanctuary in Jordan, established by the Royal Society for the Conservation of Nature in 1975. It is in the city of Zarqa in the Azraq region in the Shaumari Valley region. This reserve was established in 1975 AD near Azraq in the Eastern Desert, and its area has been designated to re-release the Arabian Oryx, which has begun to become extinct and in which species of wild birds breed. Visitors to the reserve can take a safari trip among wild animals.</string>
    <string name="halabat_Title">Al Hallabat Palace</string>
    <string name="halabat_Description">On the site of Qasr al-Hallabat there was originally a Roman fort, built up from the beginning of the 2nd century AD on a former Nabatean outpost, as part of the Limes Arabicus (the Arabian frontier). Extended in 4th century AD, the fort was abandoned and then heavily damaged by the earthquake of 551 AD. Afterwards it was transformed into a monastery and a palace by the Ghassanids, using older black basaltic rock blocks to expand the Roman remains.</string>
    <string name="main_Title">Main Bathrooms</string>
    <string name="main_Description">Main Hammamet is a natural tourist site south of the Jordanian capital, Amman. Next page From the next page to 63 home pages</string>
    <string name="wadi_Title">Wadi Mujib</string>
    <string name="wadi_Description">Deep gorge for hiking and kayaking</string>
    <string name="rum_Title">Wadi Rum</string>
    <string name="rum_Description">Wadi Rum, also called the Valley of the Moon due to the similarity of its terrain with that of the Moon, is a tourist valley located in the Hasma Desert in southern Jordan, 70 km north of the coastal city of Aqaba. Wadi Rum is the common name used in the media for the whole region. Although most of the tourist sites and camps are located outside the village of Rum.It is characterized by the presence of relatively high mountains in it, as it has the highest mountain peaks in the south of the Levant, namely: Jabal Umm al-Dami and Jabal Ram.</string>
    <string name="karak_Title">Karak Castle</string>
    <string name="karak_Description">Karak Castle is one of the largest and most important castles in Jordan. It has an area of 25,300 square meters and is about 1,000 meters above sea level. Its establishment dates back to the Moabite era. It was used by the Nabataeans, as evidenced by the presence of Nabatean statues inscribed in the first foundations of the castle. In the Byzantine era, it remained a protective shield for Jordan, as indicated by the Madaba mosaic map among the group of castles of this region. In the Islamic conquests, the Muslim armies under the leadership of Abu Ubaidah Amer bin Al-Jarrah knocked it down and surrendered to him.</string>


</resources>